## Limor Ofri

## Front-end web developer

054-2335130

ofrilim@gmail.com limor-ofri

my portfolio ofrilim

A recent bootcamp graduate looking for a full time front-end web developer position. After many years in the cosmetics industry, I made a career-changing move and learned to code. I am a quick learner, passionate about coding and building beautiful and responsive applications. In my free time I volunteer at the She Codes organization, working on expanding my knowledge of web technologies and teaching Lambada. I began my studies towards Computer Science B.Sc at The Open University this year.

## **Education**

9/2019 - 1/2020 Web Development Bootcamp at Coding Academy.

Intensive coding course (~600 hours) that covers all fundamentals of web development.

**Professional Experience** 

8/2020 - Present Front-end developer at Liveatip.

Development and maintenance of the company's website and mobile app (Vue.js, Quasar).

1/2020 - Present Instructor at She Codes, Tel Aviv University branch, volunteer.

In charge of front-end development courses. In-person teaching and tutoring women through

their first steps in coding.

4/2021 Elevators Routing System: Manage calls to elevators in a building.

> Tech stack: React.js, SCSS. Link to code Visit App

9/2019 - 5/2020 Minesweeper.

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Visit App Link to code

Meme Creator: Create your own meme. Features: upload, share and download.

Tech stack: HTML, CSS and JavaScript using MVC design patterns.

Visit App Link to code

Email: Team work. 2 applications in one.

Tech stack: Vue.js, CSS and Local Storage web Api.

Visit App Link to code

**BGood**: E-commerce clothes and accessories app.

Tech stack: Vue.is, Vuex and SCSS at the Front and Node.is with express. MongoDB,

Socket.io at the back-end.

Visit App Link to code - Frontend Link to code - Backend

1/2019 - 9/2019 Office manager at TipRanks.

2008 - 2019 Self employed in the field of Cosmetics.

**Tech Skills** 

JavaScript (ES6), HTML5 Vue.js, Vuex, Quasar

React.js, jQuery

MongoDB

. Git, GitHub, VSCode

CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap

Ajax, Axios

\* REST APIs, Web sockets

Node.js, Express.js

**Military Service** 

2002 - 2004 Completed the mandatory service as a squad commander training new recruits.